<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smart Sprout Content Services | Web Design | SEO on Sculpt and Shape Personal Training</title>
    <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Smart Sprout Content Services | Web Design | SEO on Sculpt and Shape Personal Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sculptandshape.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy | Smart Sprout</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 01:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This website has been provided for information pertaining to Smart Sprout and our services. The below information sets out how Smart Sprout uses and protects the data collected via our website.
When using this site, you are legally bound to the following privacy policy, so please read carefully. Privacy protection is something that Smart Sprout are fully committed towards and we thoroughly support the implementation of the GDPR as we feel that it important for people to be able to understand and control their own data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amrita Singh Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/amrita-singh-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/amrita-singh-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I have lost a total of 14 inches round my waist and dropped from an 18/20 to a 12/14” — Amrita Singh
I remember vividly after, our consultation where I had constant questions such as:
Would I be able to keep up? Will it be hard? Mike mentioned words such as “squats and lunges” and I remember recoiling back in horror at the very mention of them. Looking back now I know why these questions appeared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dilip Vaghela Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/dilip-vaghela-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/dilip-vaghela-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I am leaner then I was ever before and I have lost over 18kg” — Dilip Vaghela
Over the years I have tried many diets and training programmes, which all ended up in me putting on more weight than I initially started with. This led to me to becoming demotivated and feeling unhappy in the way I looked.
In March 2008 I thought enough was enough and I decided that I was going to lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiona Allan Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/fiona-allan-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/fiona-allan-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“Over seven months I lost five stone, gained fitness and muscle tone, and totally transformed the way I think about food and eating.” — Fiona Allan, CEO, Birmingham Hippodrome
Mike Kirk changed my life. When I met him, I was an extremely unhealthy weight, totally unfit, and ate and drank whatever I liked whenever I liked. Comfort eating, snacking all day, alcohol every night, coffee to wake me up the next day: a cycle that had gone on for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Dunkley Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/steve-dunkley-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/steve-dunkley-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I was shocked that I lost 1.5 stone in only 6 weeks” — Steve Dunkley I started training with Mike in October with an intention to lose my excess fat and gain muscle. He gave me all the advice I needed to change my diet and live a healthy active lifestyle. The information on his website was also a really useful resource and the recipes were great. I especially liked the smoothies as they were not only useful as a weight loss tool, but they tasted fantastic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Mike</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Qualifications and Experience I been actively involved in the fitness industry for over 20 years and have been qualified as a personal trainer for 18 years.
Aside from being a YMCA level 3 personal trainer, I have also studied nutrition, circuits and kettle-bell training.
My training perspective I believe that, to achieve a great body, you must first master your diet, you should eat healthily before they even think about breaking a sweat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are personal trainers up to the task?</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/are-personal-trainers-up-to-the-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/are-personal-trainers-up-to-the-job/</guid>
      <description>Credit where credit&amp;rsquo;s due. Many trainers (not all) that I have met have a good grasp on both fitness and weight training.
However, few have any understanding of the body, human dietary needs and the true reason we all aim to improve our bodies.
Note: though a number of trainers that I know are competent in the gym, many unsuspecting gym instructors and lifeguards have now been pressured into this role by health clubs and gyms in an attempt to squeeze more money from their members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claim a free week | Sculpt and Shape PT Leicester</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/free-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/free-week/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claudia&#39;s Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/claudias-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/claudias-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I have lost just over two stone so far” — Claudia Pearlman, Care Worker. I had been overweight for years and as confident as I came across to people that I was fine with how I looked, inside I was a mess. So when I met Mike in November 2008, I was very happy and ready for him to step in.
Straight away on the initial consultation with Mike I knew he was going to change my life and health for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact | Smart Sprout</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave&#39;s Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/daves-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/daves-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I lost a stone in the first week” — Dave Chadwick I came across Sculpt &amp;amp; Shape when I met Mike in the gym. I have been using the gym for many years, but only over the last 12 months has it become very important to me, as it helps me to focus and unwind after a day at work. I have had personal training before and had not been overly impressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed&#39;s Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/eds-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/eds-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“Even Though it has been 5 weeks with him, I have amazingly lost 1.5 Stone in weight” — Ed Rex Okay, like you, I was reading these testimonials and thinking what does this guy, Mike Kirk, have to offer me? Can Mike give me results? Can Mike help me stay in the results? Two words — HELL Yeah! I do admit that with some trepidation when I was meeting with him for my consultation that I thought he would be one of those personal trainers that are only after your money and give you a bog-standard fitness programme that’s not tailored to your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic &amp; Chive Veggie Burger Recipe</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/garlic-chive-veggie-burger-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/garlic-chive-veggie-burger-recipe/</guid>
      <description>You will need:  A food processor White kidney beans (2x tins) Butter beans (1x small tin) ½ chopped onion Crushed garlic (4 cloves) Chives (2 tbsp) 4-6 heaped tbsp gluten free flour A splash of vegetable oil Salt (⅓ tsp) Black pepper (½ tsp) Turmeric (⅓ tsp)  Garlic and Chive Veggie Burger
What to do:  Add the onion, garlic, black pepper, turmeric &amp;amp; salt into the food processor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How sugar is killing you</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/how-sugar-is-killing-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/how-sugar-is-killing-you/</guid>
      <description>You might think I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about sugar making you fat&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not!
Sugar (I mean refined sugar &amp;ndash; cane, palm, coconut, rice syrup, pasteurised fruit juice&amp;hellip;)
When I say &amp;lsquo;sugar&amp;rsquo; I am referring to any sugar which is no longer part of a living fruit or vegetable.
Why is sugar so bad?
Sugar causes deficiencies Stripped from its natural origin, sugar is void of the enzymes and nutrients necessary to break it down into glycogen and assimilate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a superfood smoothie</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/how-to-make-a-superfood-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/how-to-make-a-superfood-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>What you need&amp;hellip; - Blender
- Two ripe bananas
- 2 Handfuls of frozen Blueberries
- 1 teaspoon of Flaxseed oil*
- 1 Teaspoon of Hemp seed oil*
- Two Spirulina tablets*
- Half a Lime
- Small cup of water
- A pint glass
How it&amp;rsquo;s done Step 1 - Place the two peeled bananas into the blender
Step 2 - Add your 2 handful of Blueberries
Step 3 - Add a teaspoon of Flaxseed oil and Hemp seed oil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Losing weight is easier than you think!</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/losing-weight-is-easier-than-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/losing-weight-is-easier-than-you-think/</guid>
      <description>1/2 – 1 stone per month! Sound too good to be true? A 5 stone loss should be achieved in 5 to 10 months.
So why does weight loss seem so hard to achieve? Most people attempt to lose weight through calorie cutting/measuring and long duration exercise. Both are a complete waste of time. As your body will swiftly regulate its requirement, just as it does your requirement of oxygen (as you increase your aerobic fitness).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neal&#39;s Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/neals-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/neals-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I’ve lost almost 2 stone, in weight, and 6 inches from my waist.” — Neal Harris, NHS Manager. I’ve been training with Mike for six months and the physical results speak for themselves: I’ve lost almost 2 stone, in weight, and 6 inches from my waist. Sessions with Mike aren’t just about physical well-being, they’re about mental well-being too. My confidence levels have increased loads over the past few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Prices for personal training sessions vary based on session frequency. Below are my prices:
4 sessions weekly = £27.50 per session
3 sessions weekly = £31 per session
2 sessions weekly = £35 per session
Programmes, support and dietary advice are all included in the price. I take a “your goal is my goal” approach, so I include everything needed to get your result.
If you have any custom requirements, get in touch today and I will do my best to accommodate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The false mantra of fitness trainers</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/the-false-mantra-of-fitness-trainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/the-false-mantra-of-fitness-trainers/</guid>
      <description>Have you had poor results when following the advice of fitness instructors or personal trainers?
You may have noticed a pattern/trend in their advice:
 High protein Low calorie/calorie counting Low carb Paleo/Ketogenic diets HIT or other high impact training&amp;hellip;  Unfortunately, the science doesn&amp;rsquo;t back up these techniques &amp;mdash; they are oversimplified and these methods could do you harm.
The fact of the matter is, low calorie diets and calorie “burning” routines just don&amp;rsquo;t work in the long term, which has been proven: [</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/training-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/training-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Your body reflects your health and a healthy body is lean and adequately muscled.
The Calorie/Furnace Myth You have likely heard that weight loss is simply the practice of using (or burning) more energy/calories than you consume. Not only is this a misleading over-simplification, it has been proven wrong. [
The Look AHEAD Trial: A Review and Discussion Of Its Outcomes
The LookAhead trial was a randomized controlled trial comparing an Intensive Lifestyle Intervention (ILI) to a Diabetes Support and Education (DSE) in overweight and obese type 2 diabetes patients to track the development of cardiovascular disease over &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you can&#39;t lose weight</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/why-you-cant-lose-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/advice/why-you-cant-lose-weight/</guid>
      <description>Most of us like to be in good shape. However, few people are able to reach their ideal or even come close.
This is because we have been taught to think about food wrongly.
There are, likely, two main problems with your diet:
 You are addicted to certain foods Many of the foods you need to satisfy your body (and avoid deficiency) are missing or in short supply  There is no way to exercise away a poor diet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
