<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>speed on Sculpt and Shape Personal Training</title>
    <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/categories/speed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in speed on Sculpt and Shape Personal Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sculptandshape.co.uk/categories/speed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amrita Singh Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/amrita-singh-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/amrita-singh-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I have lost a total of 14 inches round my waist and dropped from an 18/20 to a 12/14” — Amrita Singh
I remember vividly after, our consultation where I had constant questions such as:
Would I be able to keep up? Will it be hard? Mike mentioned words such as “squats and lunges” and I remember recoiling back in horror at the very mention of them. Looking back now I know why these questions appeared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dilip Vaghela Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/dilip-vaghela-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/dilip-vaghela-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I am leaner then I was ever before and I have lost over 18kg” — Dilip Vaghela
Over the years I have tried many diets and training programmes, which all ended up in me putting on more weight than I initially started with. This led to me to becoming demotivated and feeling unhappy in the way I looked.
In March 2008 I thought enough was enough and I decided that I was going to lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiona Allan Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/fiona-allan-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/fiona-allan-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“Over seven months I lost five stone, gained fitness and muscle tone, and totally transformed the way I think about food and eating.” — Fiona Allan, CEO, Birmingham Hippodrome
Mike Kirk changed my life. When I met him, I was an extremely unhealthy weight, totally unfit, and ate and drank whatever I liked whenever I liked. Comfort eating, snacking all day, alcohol every night, coffee to wake me up the next day: a cycle that had gone on for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Dunkley Weight Loss Testimonial</title>
      <link>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/steve-dunkley-weight-loss-testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sculptandshape.co.uk/testimonials/steve-dunkley-weight-loss-testimonial/</guid>
      <description>“I was shocked that I lost 1.5 stone in only 6 weeks” — Steve Dunkley I started training with Mike in October with an intention to lose my excess fat and gain muscle. He gave me all the advice I needed to change my diet and live a healthy active lifestyle. The information on his website was also a really useful resource and the recipes were great. I especially liked the smoothies as they were not only useful as a weight loss tool, but they tasted fantastic!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
